Can the girl who never speaks... Become the voice of a generation?
Radio Rebel is a comedy, drama, family film directed by Peter Howitt.
High school senior Tara is so painfully shy that she dreads speaking to
anyone in the hallways or getting called on in class.
But in the privacy of her bedroom with her iPod in hand, she rocks out -- doing mock broadcasts
for Miami's hottest FM radio station, which happens to be owned by her stepfather.
When a slot opens up at The SLAM, Tara surprises herself by blossoming behind the mike
into confident, "Radio Rebel" -- and to everyone's shock, she's a hit!
Tara, played by Debby Ryan.
Audrey, played by Sarena Parmar.
Gavin, played by Adam DiMarco.
Gabe, played by Atticus Mitchell.
Stacy, played by Merritt Patterson.
Kim, played by Allie Bertram.
Radio Rebel is a 2012 teen drama television film directed by Peter Howitt, written by
Erik Patterson and Jessica Scott, based on the novel Shrinking Violet.
The movie premiered on Disney Channel on February 17, 2012.
The movie was produced by MarVista Entertainment and Two 4 the
Money Media, in association with Disney Channel.
It stars Debby Ryan, Merritt Patterson, Adam DiMarco,
Sarena Parmar and Nancy Robertson.
The film follows a shy girl (Ryan) who goes undercover with a radio
persona that allows her to express her true feelings.
Her identity is put at risk when her school principal (Robertson)
threatens to expel the young girl following a life of mischief.
The film explores themes of high school, jealousy, parent
child relationship, shyness, secret identity.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.